// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Water ______ at a temperature of 100°C.",
    answer: "boils",
    options: [
      "is to boil",
      "is boiling",
      "boils",
      "boiled"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "In some countries _______ very hot all the time.",
    answer: "it is",
    options: [
      "there is",
      "is",
      "it is",
      "is it"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "In cold countries people wear thick clothes ______ warm.",
    answer: "to keep",
    options: [
      "for keeping",
      "to keep",
      "for to keep",
      "to keeping"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "In England people are always talking about ______.",
    answer: "the weather",
    options: [
      "a weather",
      "the weather",
      "weather",
      "an weather"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "In some places ______ almost every day.",
    answer: "it rains",
    options: [
      "it rains",
      "there rains",
      "it raining",
      "rains"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "In deserts there isn´t ______ grass.",
    answer: "any",
    options: [
      "the",
      "some",
      "few",
      "any"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Places near the Equator have ______ weather even in the cold season.",
    answer: "a warm",
    options: [
      "a warm",
      "warm",
      "too warm",
      "the warm"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "In England ______ time of year is usually from December to February.",
    answer: "the coldest",
    options: [
      "coldest",
      "colder",
      "a cold",
      "the coldest"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "______ people don´t know what it´s like in other countries.",
    answer: "Most",
    options: [
      "Most of",
      "Most",
      "The most",
      "Of most"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Very ______ people can travel abroad",
    answer: "few",
    options: [
      "small",
      "less",
      "little",
      "few"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "In some countries students have to spend a lot of time working ______ their own.",
    answer: "on",
    options: [
      "by",
      "at",
      "in",
      "on"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "There aren´t ______ easy ways of learning a foreign language in your own country",
    answer: "any",
    options: [
      "no",
      "any",
      "none",
      "some"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];